Hey Traveler, I'll let you in on a little secret. Did you know there are monsters that come out at night in Mondstadt?
Hé, je vais te dire un petit secret ! Tu savais qu'il y a des monstres qui apparaissent la nuit à Mondstadt ?
Shh, be quiet!
Chut ! Moins fort...
I'll tell you everything, but you can't tell nobody!
Je vais tout te raconter, mais garde-le pour toi !
After everyone is tucked up cozy in their beds for the night
Quand tout le monde dort la nuit,
Monsters pretending to be Knights of Favonius come out to trick people!
des monstres dupent les gens en se faisant passer pour des chevaliers de l'Ordre !
I could even hear their footsteps from inside the confinement room...
Je pouvais entendre le bruit de leurs pas depuis ma cellule...
And soooo... BOOM! I blasted the door open to defend Mondstadt from the monsters!
et... BOUM !! J'ai fait sauter la porte pour voler au secours de Mondstadt !
But the Master Jean who grabbed me and dragged me away was really scary... Scary like the real Master Jean, not like some monster... So strange...
Mais le monstre déguisé en Jean m'a attrapée et j'ai eu si peur ! Elle était aussi effrayante que la vraie... Étrange...
Anywho, you mustn't tell a soul!
Bref, tu ne dois rien dire à personne !
Kaeya's the one who told me the secret about the monsters. He didn't tell nobody else but me!
C'est Kaeya qui m'a dit pour les monstres ! Il n'y a que moi qui connaît ce secret !
Oh, Kaeya... Coaxing Klee into escaping from solitary confinement, it seems...
Kaeya a encore incité Klee à s'échapper de détention...
Hehehe, perhaps we've made the child's studies a little too imaginative lately?
Nous avons peut-être été trop indulgents avec elle ces derniers temps...